[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 5, "question": "How many gun murders were there in Britain?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "gun", "murders", "were", "there", "in", "Britain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 6, "answer": "How many great white sharks --", "answer_tokens": ["How", "many", "great", "white", "sharks", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex Jones"]}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "What was your overall reaction to that extraordinary exchange with Alex Jones last night?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "overall", "reaction", "to", "that", "extraordinary", "exchange", "with", "Alex", "Jones", "last", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Well, I mean, as somebody who favors more gun control, I really hope that Alex Jones does more TV, because, you know, look, you've been quite articulate in making the case for gun control.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "as", "somebody", "who", "favors", "more", "gun", "control", ",", "I", "really", "hope", "that", "Alex", "Jones", "does", "more", "TV", ",", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "look", ",", "you", "'ve", "been", "quite", "articulate", "in", "making", "the", "case", "for", "gun", "control", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex Jones"], "TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "-- that he raised about the actual argument?", "question_tokens": ["--", "that", "he", "raised", "about", "the", "actual", "argument", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Let me -- he made one substantial -- they've made two substantial arguments.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "--", "he", "made", "one", "substantial", "--", "they", "'ve", "made", "two", "substantial", "arguments", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex Jones"]}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "What did you make of what Alex Jones' performance was like and what does it tell you about that kind of gun rights on the rather extreme side of the gun rights lobby?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "what", "Alex", "Jones", "'", "performance", "was", "like", "and", "what", "does", "it", "tell", "you", "about", "that", "kind", "of", "gun", "rights", "on", "the", "rather", "extreme", "side", "of", "the", "gun", "rights", "lobby", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Well, to me it was really a fairly typical performance for Alex Jones.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "to", "me", "it", "was", "really", "a", "fairly", "typical", "performance", "for", "Alex", "Jones", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex Jones"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Is it going to be successful?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "going", "to", "be", "successful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "I fear that it is not going to be very successful.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "fear", "that", "it", "is", "not", "going", "to", "be", "very", "successful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJR", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "So why can't we begin to have the same kind of public health approach, not to ban guns, but to make them a little bit safer in American homes?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "ca", "n't", "we", "begin", "to", "have", "the", "same", "kind", "of", "public", "health", "approach", ",", "not", "to", "ban", "guns", ",", "but", "to", "make", "them", "a", "little", "bit", "safer", "in", "American", "homes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "And harder to get, the more extreme variety of weapon, for those who may be disturbed.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "harder", "to", "get", ",", "the", "more", "extreme", "variety", "of", "weapon", ",", "for", "those", "who", "may", "be", "disturbed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "What was your reaction to that as somebody who lost a loved one in the Aurora massacre?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "to", "that", "as", "somebody", "who", "lost", "a", "loved", "one", "in", "the", "Aurora", "massacre", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "NN", "WP", "RB", "DT", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Initially, I was infuriated and disturbed by his reaction.", "answer_tokens": ["Initially", ",", "I", "was", "infuriated", "and", "disturbed", "by", "his", "reaction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Aurora"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Do you believe that there is now momentum to get real action or not?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "there", "is", "now", "momentum", "to", "get", "real", "action", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "I'm cautiously optimistic.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "cautiously", "optimistic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "What's the difference?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "The car is not specifically mentioned in the Bill of Rights.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "car", "is", "not", "specifically", "mentioned", "in", "the", "Bill", "of", "Rights", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Why would you want to give one of these killing machines to one of your children, anyway?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "want", "to", "give", "one", "of", "these", "killing", "machines", "to", "one", "of", "your", "children", ",", "anyway", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "First off, we don't own M-4s or M-16s.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "off", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "own", "M-4s", "or", "M-16s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "So your answer is that everybody in a movie theater would be armed with an AR-15?", "question_tokens": ["So", "your", "answer", "is", "that", "everybody", "in", "a", "movie", "theater", "would", "be", "armed", "with", "an", "AR-15", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "No, that's not what I said.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "that", "'s", "not", "what", "I", "said", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Where does that lead America to other than utter Wild West hell?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "that", "lead", "America", "to", "other", "than", "utter", "Wild", "West", "hell", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "TO", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "All right.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Do you believe that Sandy Hook represents any kind of tipping point in favor of new gun legislation?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "Sandy", "Hook", "represents", "any", "kind", "of", "tipping", "point", "in", "favor", "of", "new", "gun", "legislation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "No, I think America is a country that revels in violence, that was born in violence, that loves the image of the frontiersman and the cowboy and having guns.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "America", "is", "a", "country", "that", "revels", "in", "violence", ",", "that", "was", "born", "in", "violence", ",", "that", "loves", "the", "image", "of", "the", "frontiersman", "and", "the", "cowboy", "and", "having", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sandy Hook"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "How do we try to move forward to a point of some consensus, where the gun lobby are persuaded that these AR-15 type, military-type machine guns, what they really are, are actually not part of this debate in any sane way?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "we", "try", "to", "move", "forward", "to", "a", "point", "of", "some", "consensus", ",", "where", "the", "gun", "lobby", "are", "persuaded", "that", "these", "AR-15", "type", ",", "military-type", "machine", "guns", ",", "what", "they", "really", "are", ",", "are", "actually", "not", "part", "of", "this", "debate", "in", "any", "sane", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Well, I think, Piers, that it begins with a discussion in the court of public opinion.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", ",", "Piers", ",", "that", "it", "begins", "with", "a", "discussion", "in", "the", "court", "of", "public", "opinion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "RP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Do you hold out any hope that if it does go to Congress, they'll pass anything involving gun control legislation?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "hold", "out", "any", "hope", "that", "if", "it", "does", "go", "to", "Congress", ",", "they", "'ll", "pass", "anything", "involving", "gun", "control", "legislation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "I do want to point out, based on the conversation last night, that it's not even worth mentioning this guy's name.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "want", "to", "point", "out", ",", "based", "on", "the", "conversation", "last", "night", ",", "that", "it", "'s", "not", "even", "worth", "mentioning", "this", "guy", "'s", "name", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Buzz Bissinger"]}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Because they just want to be re-elected at the end of the day, right?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "they", "just", "want", "to", "be", "re-elected", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "day", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "But Buzz Bissinger, this is all well and good.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "Buzz", "Bissinger", ",", "this", "is", "all", "well", "and", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Well, I feel that they are afraid.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "feel", "that", "they", "are", "afraid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Why does anyone need multiple rounds?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "does", "anyone", "need", "multiple", "rounds", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "No one needs any of that stuff.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "one", "needs", "any", "of", "that", "stuff", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "First of all, how is your client?", "question_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "how", "is", "your", "client", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Thank you for asking, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "for", "asking", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Does she really know what happened to her?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "she", "really", "know", "what", "happened", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Well, that's the case.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "If not, are there witnesses you think who will be able to?", "question_tokens": ["If", "not", ",", "are", "there", "witnesses", "you", "think", "who", "will", "be", "able", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "ITZSIMMONS: Well, there were already other witnesses that testified at the preliminary.", "answer_tokens": ["ITZSIMMONS", ":", "Well", ",", "there", "were", "already", "other", "witnesses", "that", "testified", "at", "the", "preliminary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "How do you defend him?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "defend", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Quite simply.", "answer_tokens": ["Quite", "simply", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Does your client accept that he behaved badly on the night, just generally?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "your", "client", "accept", "that", "he", "behaved", "badly", "on", "the", "night", ",", "just", "generally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "He is 16 years old.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "16", "years", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Do you believe that there is sufficient doubt about your client's involvement in the sexual aspect of this case, that he will be acquitted?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "there", "is", "sufficient", "doubt", "about", "your", "client", "'s", "involvement", "in", "the", "sexual", "aspect", "of", "this", "case", ",", "that", "he", "will", "be", "acquitted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Look, I'm not here to do what social media is doing, OK.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "here", "to", "do", "what", "social", "media", "is", "doing", ",", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]